Guide to the Nigeria Collection
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Additional Material, 1960-2005; Accession 2010-M-075
  - Publications, reports, and speeches
    - We Build in Vain, by G. O. Olusanya, Obafemi Awolowo Memorial Lecture Series, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Posters
    - Educare Trust Teaching Aid poster on civic education, Undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - AIDS posters (3), issued by the Community People's Action Against AIDS, 2002-2003 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Law Enforcement Education poster, Undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Oyo State Executive Council members poster, Undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Calendar with image of Kabiru Mai Kaba and presumed political leaders, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Additional material, 1959-2013; Accession 2015-M-001
  - Printed material, 1959-2013 (Box 1, Folder 1-5)
  - Posters, 2000s (Folder 2)